# Arthur Luís Lima Bender

Full-Stack Developer

PERSONAL DETAILS

**Date of Birth** 17/02/2001

**Nationality** Brazil

## **Phone**

+55 48 99606-3778

#### **Email**

arthurllbender@gmail.com

## Links

github.com/ArthurBender linkedin.com/in/Arthur-Bender

## SOFT SKILLS

- Problem solving;
- Long-term focus;
- Communication;
- Project and people management;

- Desire to learn.

# **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese English

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a full-stack developer with more than 5 years of experience in the field, passionate about technology and development. I really enjoy learning and I am a lively and positive person, facilitating teamwork. In recent years, I've mainly developed projects using Ruby on Rails, both frontend and backend, with focus on user interaction.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE



**DBA Tecnologia -** Mid-Level Full-Stack Developer Brazil Jul 2021 - Present

- Creation and maintenance of modular web applications in Ruby on Rails;
- Android application development in Java using interactive map systems;
- Python APIs development using Flask;
- Maintenance of Docker containers;
- Interactions and maintenance in Postgres and Redis databases.



**DBA Tecnologia -** Junior Full-Stack Developer Brazil Feb 2019 - Jul 2021

- Web applications development using frontend languages and the Bootstrap styling framework;
- Usage of SCRUM methodology;
- Integration of web applications with Google services (Maps, Vision);
- Maintenance of applications in Ruby on Rails.



**DBA Tecnologia -** Web Development Intern Brazil Ago 2017 - Fev 2019

- Development of web applications in Python focused on interaction with the Linux command line;
- Maintenance of web applications using PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **IT Management Degree**

Instituto Federal de Santa Catarina 2020 - 2022 G.P.A: 9.2

## **High School**

Escola Waldorf Anabá 2017 - 2019